Today it has been 6 months since grandfather passed away,
but do you know
what happens in the house after 6 months of someone's death?  So as soon as
morning came, mom and I left for younger
grandfather's house.  As soon as I reached here, I saw that
everyone was busy preparing pure and sacred food.
Aunty is making Batu and Puri here.
What do you call Batu here
?  Please do tell in the comments.  This is
my grandfather's youngest sister.  Then Pandit
ji performed Pind Puja for the peace of grandfather.
Grandpa, wherever you are, stay healthy
and happy.  You are still alive in our hearts.
Now Pandit ji
vaccinated everyone one by one.  The food
is ready here.  First I fed all the relatives and
then I also ate.  They say that
everyone comes in times of happiness.
In times of sorrow, we come to know who is our own and who is a stranger.